### **ARAVIND MS**

MUNDACKAL HOUSE, AMBALAMEDU P O, KUZHIKKADU, ERNAKULAM, PIN:682303 msaravind999@gmail.com

## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

I am familiar with multiple programming languages and have good problem solving skills obtained through online coding competitions. I have basic experience with android development and web page development. My biggest aim is to work as a computer programmer to challenge complex problems and develop efficient solution to complex problems

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

**Programming Languages:** C, C++, Java, Python, HTML, Java script

**Operating Systems:** Windows, Linux

Applications: Microsoft Office, Microsoft powerpoint, Spreadsheet

#### **EDUCATION**

2017-2021: APJ ABDUL KALAM TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science

2016: 12th (senior secondary examination)

State board of secondary education

2014: 10th (secondary examination)
State board of secondary education

#### EXPERIENCE

GOFREELAB TECHNOLOGIES PVT LTD Kochi, Kerala May 30 2018 – June 16 2018

INTERNSHIP: BASIC STUDY ON JAVA SE8

**INDIVIDUAL PROJECTS** 

SAMPLE CALCULATOR AND LOGIN PAGE USING ANDROID STUDIO

**GROUP PROJECTS** 

DIARYGENIE-AN ONLINE DIARY SYSTEM

**EVENTS** 

.HACK() Hackathon 2020

Workshop on django-Attendee

Workshop on blockchain-Attendee

Workshop on Android studio-Attendee

# **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

IEEE student volunteer(2017-present)

ISTE student volunteer(2017-present)

Google student developer club(2017-present)